<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><all-authors>
<author><id>1</id><fullName>Joanne Rowling</fullName>
<profile>In 1995, Rowling finished her manuscript for Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone which 
was typed on an old manual typewriter. Upon the enthusiastic response of Bryony Evens, a reader who 
had been asked to review the book's first three chapters, the Fulham-based Christopher Little Literary 
Agency agreed to represent Rowling in her quest for a publisher. The book was submitted to twelve 
publishing houses, all of which rejected the manuscript. A year later, she was finally given the green 
light (and a £1,500 advance) by editor Barry Cunningham from Bloomsbury, a publishing house in London. 
The decision to publish Rowling's book owes much to Alice Newton, the eight-year-old daughter of Bloomsbury's 
chairman, who was given the first chapter to review by her father and immediately demanded the next. Although 
Bloomsbury agreed to publish the book, Cunningham says that he advised Rowling to get a day job, since she had 
little chance of making money in children's books. Soon after, in 1997, Rowling received an £8,000 grant from 
the Scottish Arts Council to enable her to continue writing</profile>
</author>
<author><id>2</id><fullName>Andrzej Sapkowski</fullName>
<profile>Sapkowski studied economics at the University of Łódź, and before turning to writing, he had worked 
as a senior sales representative for a foreign trade company. He started his literary career as a translator, 
in particular, of science fiction. He says he wrote his first short story, "The Witcher" ("Wiedźmin", also 
translated "The Hexer" or "Spellmaker") on a whim, in order to enter a contest by Polish science fiction and 
fantasy magazine Fantastyka. In an interview, he said that being a businessman at the time and thus familiar 
with marketing, he knew how to sell, and indeed, he won the 3rd prize. The story was published in Fantastyka 
in 1986 and was enormously successful both with readers and critics. Sapkowski has created a cycle of tales 
based on the world of "The Witcher", comprising three collections of short stories and five novels. This cycle 
and his other works have made him one of the best-known fantasy authors in Poland in the 1990s. The main character 
of "The Witcher" is Geralt of Rivia, a monster hunter trained for this since childhood. Geralt exists in a morally 
ambiguous universe, yet manages to maintain his own coherent code of ethics. At the same time cynical and noble, 
Geralt has been compared to Raymond Chandler's signature character Philip Marlowe. The world in which these 
adventures take place is heavily influenced by Slavic mythology.</profile>
</author>
<author><id>3</id><fullName>Mikhail Afanasyevich Bulgakov</fullName>
<profile>During his life, Bulgakov was best known for the plays he contributed to Konstantin Stanislavski's 
and Nemirovich-Danchenko's Moscow Art Theatre. Stalin was known to be fond of the play Days of the Turbins 
(Дни Турбиных) (1926), which was based on Bulgakov's novel The White Guard. His dramatization of Molière's 
life in The Cabal of Hypocrites (Кабала святош, 1936) is still performed by the Moscow Art Theatre. Even after 
his plays were banned from the theatres, Bulgakov wrote a comedy about Ivan the Terrible's visit into 1930s 
Moscow. His play Batum (1939) about the early years of Stalin was prohibited by the premier himself. Bulgakov 
began writing prose with The White Guard (Белая гвардия)– a novel about a life of a White Army officer's family 
in civil war Kiev. In the mid-1920s, he came to admire the works of H. G. Wells and wrote several stories with e
lements of science fiction, notably The Fatal Eggs (Роковые яйца) (1924) and Heart of a Dog (Собачье сердце) (1925). 
He intended to compile his stories of the mid-twenties (published mostly in medical journals) that were based on 
his work as a country doctor in 1916–1918 into a collection titled Notes of a Young Doctor (Записки юного врача), 
but he died before he could publish it.</profile>
</author>
<author><id>4</id><fullName>Mark Frost</fullName>
<profile>Mark Frost was born on November 25, 1953 in Brooklyn, New York City, to Mary Virginia Calhoun and actor 
Warren Frost. He is the elder brother of actress Lindsay Frost and writer and photographer Scott Frost. During his 
childhood, Frost was raised in Los Angeles, California and spent his adolescence in Minneapolis, Minnesota, where he 
attended Marshall-University High School. As a high-school student, he spent two years on an internship program studying 
and working at Minneapolis' Guthrie Theater. Frost subsequently enrolled in Carnegie Mellon University (CMU) in Pittsburgh, 
Pennsylvania, studying acting, directing and playwriting. During his time in college, he worked as a member of the lighting 
crew on PBS' Mister Rogers' Neighborhood alongside actor Michael Keaton. Frost graduated from CMU in 1975 with a Bachelor 
of Fine Arts. After his graduation, he returned to the Guthrie Theater in Minneapolis, where he was a literary associate 
until 1978.</profile>
</author>
<author><id>5</id><fullName>Eric Arthur Blair 
(George Orwell)</fullName>
<profile>Eric Arthur Blair was born on 25 June 1903 in Motihari, Bihar, British India. His great-grandfather, Charles Blair, 
was a wealthy country gentleman in Dorset who married Lady Mary Fane, daughter of the Earl of Westmorland, and had income as 
an absentee landlord of plantations in Jamaica. His grandfather, Thomas Richard Arthur Blair, was a clergyman. Eric Blair 
described his family as "lower-upper-middle class". His father, Richard Walmesley Blair, worked in the Opium Department of 
the Indian Civil Service. His mother, Ida Mabel Blair (née Limouzin), grew up in Moulmein, Burma, where her French father was 
involved in speculative ventures. Eric had two sisters: Marjorie, five years older; and Avril, five years younger. When Eric 
was one year old, his mother took him and Marjorie to England. His birthplace and ancestral house in Motihari is now a historical 
monument.</profile>
</author>

<author><id>6</id><fullName>Richard Phillips Feynman</fullName>
<profile>Richard Feynman was an American theoretical physicist, known for his work in the path integral formulation of quantum 
mechanics, the theory of quantum electrodynamics, the physics of the superfluidity of supercooled liquid helium, as well as his 
work in particle physics for which he proposed the parton model. For contributions to the development of quantum electrodynamics, 
Feynman received the Nobel Prize in Physics in 1965 jointly with Julian Schwinger and Shin'ichirō Tomonaga. He assisted in the 
development of the atomic bomb during World War II and became known to a wide public in the 1980s as a member of the Rogers 
Commission, the panel that investigated the Space Shuttle Challenger disaster. Along with his work in theoretical physics, Feynman 
has been credited with pioneering the field of quantum computing and introducing the concept of nanotechnology. He held the 
Richard C. Tolman professorship in theoretical physics at the California Institute of Technology.</profile>
</author>

<author><id>7</id><fullName>Stephen William Hawking</fullName>
<profile>Stephen William Hawking was an English theoretical physicist, cosmologist, and author who was director of research at the 
Centre for Theoretical Cosmology at the University of Cambridge at the time of his death. He was the Lucasian Professor of Mathematics 
at the University of Cambridge between 1979 and 2009. Hawking was born in Oxford into a family of doctors. Hawking began his university 
education at University College, Oxford, in October 1959 at the age of 17, where he received a first-class BA (Hons.) degree in physics. 
He began his graduate work at Trinity Hall, Cambridge, in October 1962, where he obtained his PhD degree in applied mathematics and 
theoretical physics, specialising in general relativity and cosmology in March 1966. During this period—in 1963—Hawking was diagnosed 
with an early-onset, slow-progressing form of motor neurone disease (also known as amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) or Lou Gehrig's 
disease) that gradually paralysed him over the decades. After the loss of his speech, he was able to communicate through a speech-generating 
device—initially through use of a handheld switch, and eventually by using a single cheek muscle. Hawking's scientific works included a 
collaboration with Roger Penrose on gravitational singularity theorems in the framework of general relativity and the theoretical prediction 
that black holes emit radiation, often called Hawking radiation. Initially, Hawking radiation was controversial. By the late 1970s and 
following the publication of further research, the discovery was widely accepted as a significant breakthrough in theoretical physics. 
Hawking was the first to set out a theory of cosmology explained by a union of the general theory of relativity and quantum mechanics. 
He was a vigorous supporter of the many-worlds interpretation of quantum mechanics. Hawking achieved commercial success with several 
works of popular science in which he discussed his theories and cosmology in general. His book A Brief History of Time appeared on the 
Sunday Times bestseller list for a record-breaking 237 weeks. Hawking was a Fellow of the Royal Society, a lifetime member of the Pontifical 
Academy of Sciences, and a recipient of the Presidential Medal of Freedom, the highest civilian award in the United States. In 2002, Hawking 
was ranked number 25 in the BBC's poll of the 100 Greatest Britons. He died on 14 March 2018 at the age of 76, after living with motor neurone 
disease for more than 50 years.</profile>
</author>
</all-authors>