<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?><all-descriptions>
<details>
<id>1</id>
<fullDescription>Harry Potter has been living a difficult life of abuse by his aunt and 
uncle, Vernon and Petunia Dursley and bullied by their son Dudley since the death of 
his parents ten years prior. His life changes on his eleventh birthday when he 
receives a letter of acceptance into Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, 
delivered by a half-giant named Rubeus Hagrid after previous letters had been 
destroyed by Vernon and Petunia. Hagrid reveals that Harry's parents, James 
and Lily Potter, also wizards, were murdered by the most evil and powerful dark 
wizard of all time, Lord Voldemort, resulting in Harry being sent to live with 
his aunt and uncle as a baby. Voldemort failed to kill Harry, and his powers were 
destroyed in the attempt, forcing him into exile and making Harry famous among the 
hidden magical community.</fullDescription>
</details>

<details>
<id>2</id>
<fullDescription>The King of Temeria, Foltest, has offered a reward to anyone who can 
lift the curse on his daughter, Adda (the result of an incestuous union with his late 
sister, also named Adda), who was born as a striga, and now terrorizes the town every 
night. Foltest insists that his daughter not be harmed, but reluctantly grants Geralt 
permission to kill her if Geralt decides that Adda cannot be returned to human form. A 
more difficult question, to which Geralt can give no certain answer, is whether Adda, 
who has been a monster her whole life, can live as a "normal" human even if the curse 
is lifted.</fullDescription>
</details>

<details>
<id>3</id>
<fullDescription>The novel has two settings. The first is Moscow during the 1930s, where 
Satan appears at Patriarch's Ponds as Professor Woland. He is accompanied by Koroviev, a 
grotesquely-dressed valet; Behemoth, a black cat; Azazello, a hitman; and Hella, a female 
vampire. They target the literary elite and Massolit, their trade union, whose headquarters 
is Griboyedov House. Massolit consists of corrupt social climbers and their women, 
bureaucrats, profiteers, and cynics. The second setting is the Jerusalem of Pontius Pilate: 
Pilate's trial of Yeshua Ha-Notsri (Jesus of Nazareth), his recognition of an affinity with 
(and spiritual need for) Yeshua, and his reluctant acquiescence to Yeshua's execution.
</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>4</id>
<fullDescription>Unlike Secret History, which was composed of many documents compiled by 
Major Garland Briggs, The Final Dossier contains a series of 18 FBI reports written by Agent 
Preston following the events of the entire series, which expand on the fates of several 
characters which were not explained in the television series or the previous book, and 
clarifying some apparent discrepancies between them</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>5</id>
<fullDescription>In the year 1984, civilization has been damaged by world war, civil conflict, 
and revolution. Airstrip One (formerly known as Great Britain) is a province of Oceania, one 
of the three totalitarian super-states that rule the world. It is ruled by the "Party" under 
the ideology of "Ingsoc" (a Newspeak shortening of "English Socialism") and the mysterious 
leader Big Brother, who has an intense cult of personality. The Party brutally purges out anyone 
who does not fully conform to their regime using the Thought Police and constant surveillance 
through Telescreens (two-way televisions), cameras, and hidden microphones. Those who fall out 
of favour with the Party become "unpersons", disappearing with all evidence of their existence 
destroyed.</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>6</id>
<fullDescription>The book has many stories which are lighthearted in tone, such as his fascination 
with safe-cracking, studying various languages, participating with groups of people who share 
different interests (such as biology or philosophy), and ventures into art and samba music. Other 
stories cover more serious material, including his work on the Manhattan Project (during which his 
first wife Arline Greenbaum died of tuberculosis) and his critique of the science education system 
in Brazil. The section "Monster Minds" describes his slightly nervous presentation of his graduate 
work on the Wheeler–Feynman absorber theory in front of Albert Einstein, Wolfgang Pauli, Henry Norris 
Russell, John von Neumann, and other major scientists of the time.</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>7</id>
<fullDescription>The book is divided into four sections: "Why Are We Here? Will We Survive? Will 
Technology Save Us or Destroy Us? How Can We Thrive?" Stephen Hawking at NASA's StarChild Learning 
Center, 1980s. The ten big questions that are considered include: Is there a God? How did it all 
begin? What is inside a black hole? Can we predict the future? Is time travel possible? Will we 
survive on Earth? Is there other intelligent life in the universe? Should we colonise space? Will 
artificial intelligence outsmart us? How do we shape the future?</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>8</id>
<fullDescription>--</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>9</id>
<fullDescription>--</fullDescription>
</details>

 <details>
<id>10</id>
<fullDescription>--</fullDescription>
</details>

</all-descriptions>